>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们的地址 "React" 未定义，但从未使用过。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's address
'React' is undefined but never used.
如果你想的话那也不是真的
Well, that's not actually true
if you think about it, right?
什么是被转至的 div ?
What is div being transpiled to?
>> Brian Holt: 好吧，它正转至 React.createElement，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well, it's being
transpiled to React.createElement, right?
这意味着正在使用 React 。
Which means that React is being used.
在你有 Jsx 的地方你必须要在范围内采取行动
So anywhere that you have jsx,
you actually have to have React in scope,
这要求很困难
that's a hard requirement.
原因是所有东西都被转至 React.createElement。
And the reason being is everything's
being transpiled to React.createElement.
但埃斯特林特不知道
But eslint doesn't know that.
所以说你要进口这个而且从不使用它，那是什么呢 ?
So it's saying you're importing this and
never using it, so what the hell?
> > Brian Holt: 所以，让我们来解决这个问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
let's go actually fix that.
> > Brian Holt: 我们现在就这样做，动作非常快。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We'll just do
that right now, really quick.
> > Brian Holt: 所以回到你的， >> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So come back to your,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Desktop right here,
>> Brian Holt: 并且说 npm install -D
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And say npm install -D
babel-eslint eslint-plugin-import
eslint-plugin-jsx-a11y
eslint-plugin-反应。
eslint-plugin-react.
>> Brian Holt: 这只是几件事，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So that's a few things, but
我们需要所有这些工具来确保它能正确理解 React 。
we need all of these tools to make sure
that it understands React correctly.
>> Brian Holt: 我会给你第二次把它输入出去。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'll give you
a second to type that out.
>> Brian Holt: 让我们来谈谈这些包是什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
let's talk about what these packages are.
巴伯 - 埃弗林特允许埃弗林特被巴贝尔扩充，它是一个错位的人，对吧 ?
babel-eslint allows eslint to be augmented
by Babel, which is the transpiler, right?
所以，现成的，通常是不理解 React 超级好的。
So out-of-the-box, typically,
it doesn't understand React super well.
> > Brian Holt: 这就是宝宝的工作。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
that's what babel-eslint does.
esIint-plugin-import 为您提供了一些有关导入的新规则和
esIint-plugin-import gives you some
new rules around importing and
出口这些东西，就这样你就有很好的习惯了。
exporting things, just so you have
good habits with that kind of stuff.
eslint-plugin-jsx-accessibility ，即 a11y 代表的内容，
eslint-plugin-jsx-accessibility, which
is what a11y stands for,
只是一堆无脑的让人去做的事情，对吧 ?
is just a bunch of kind of no-brainer
things to do for accessibility, right?
比如说，不要让 div 和 clickable ，对，比如说。
Like, don't make divs clickable,
right, for example.
这只会帮你抓住那些真正的
This will just kind of help
you catch those really
容易获取的内容。
easy accessibility things to do.
而埃斯皮林插件的反应将会帮助我们
And eslint-plugin-react is going to
actually help us with some other
我们需要的是额外的补救规则好吗
additional React rules that we need, okay?
把所有东西都装上
So install all that stuff.
>> Brian Holt: 在安装时，我们将转至 package.json。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And while it's installing,
we're gonna go to our package.json.
>> Brian Holt: 或者不是 package.json，而是我们的 eslint 插件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Or not package.json,
rather, but our eslint plugin,
这里就有这个
this one here.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，让我们把它放在多行上，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
let's put this on multiple lines, so
这会更容易读读
it'll be a little bit easier to read.
>> Brian Holt: 好， >> Brian Holt: 因此
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
在下面的eslint:推荐下，这些都不是超级重要的。
underneath eslint:recommended,
the order of these is not super important.
唯一的就是两个漂亮的人要到最后来，对吗 ?
The only thing is the two prettier
ones have to come at the end, right?
所以上面的一切都能符合我们的要求
So everything above it can be
in whatever order we want.
这些都是最后来的，因为这两条规则都做了
These one just have to come at the end
because all these two rules do is turn
东西都关了吧
things off, right?
你得让他们最后才能离开对吧
And you need them to be last so
that they're off, right?
但如果我放了埃皮林特 :第一，最后一件事将会发生
Whereas if I put eslint:recommended first,
the last thing that will happen will be
把那个漂亮的东西翻了
turning things on that
prettier's trying to turn off.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，第一个是 plugin:import/errors。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So the first one's
gonna be plugin:import/errors.
>> Brian Holt: plugin:reet/推荐。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: plugin:react/recommended.
>> Brian Holt: 和 plugin:jsx- a11y/推荐，类似。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
plugin:jsx- a11y/recommended, like that.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，这只是一堆规则
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so this is just gonna
be a bunch of rules that are gonna coming
从我们安装的那些插件中
in from those plugins that we installed.
我们要在这里装几个插件
We're gonna install
a couple of plugins here.
其中一个会做出反应其中一个是进口的
One of them is gonna be react,
one of them is gonna be import,
其中一个将是 jsx-a11y
and one of them is going to be jsx-a11y.
>> Brian Holt: 因此扩展了我们的规则集，对，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
extends our sets of rules, right, and
插件是针对 eslint 的新能力，对吧 ?
plugins are new abilities for
eslint, right?
所以导入，这将允许它关联如果此文件
So import, this is going to allow
it to associate that if this file
导出某些内容，此其他文件可以将其导入。
exports something,
this other file can import it.
如果不出口，就不能再进口到别的地方了，对吧 ?
And if it doesn't export, then it can't
be imported somewhere else, right?
这就是进口的原因
That's kind of what import does.
这将在了解辅助功能选项时提高一些能力。
This is going to do some more abilities
with understanding accessibility.
反应会解决很多我们的雷法问题，好吗 ?
And react is going to fix a lot
of our React problems, okay?
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们会有另一个叫做规则。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then we're gonna
have another one here called rules.
>> Brian Holt: 这是我们实际可以开启和关闭特定规则的地方。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is where we can
actually turn on and off specific rules.
我们今天不打算做道具
We're not gonna be doing prop-types today.
所以请你先关掉反动 / prop-types ， >> Brian Holt: 哪个是 0 做的，
So go ahead and turn off react/prop-types,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Which is what 0 does,
把它关了
it turns it off.
>> Brian Holt: prop-类型类似于非常弱的类型
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: prop-types
are like a very weak type
检查 React 是否可以为您执行。
checking that React can do for you.
我们将在稍后的 React 研讨会中输入 " TypeScript " 。
We're gonna get to TypeScript later
in the intermediate React workshop.
因此，当您使用 TypeScript时， prop-types 是有用的。
So prop-types are a useful
when you're using TypeScript.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 接下来，我们会说，没有控制台，那个，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then another one,
we're gonna say, no-console, that one,
把那个就在 1 号上
just turn that one on 1.
>> Brian Holt: Whoops.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Whoops.
>> Brian Holt: 我经常使用 console.log 来调试内容，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I frequently use
console.log to debug things, right?
因此，如果您没有启用控制台，那么它将不会让您，并且
And so if you have no-console enabled,
it will not let you, and
它会被排除在这方面
it will error out on that.
而 1 则是警告，对，所以
Whereas 1 will be a warning, right, so
它会是绿色的而不是红色的下划线
it'll be green underlined
instead of red underlined.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 酷，那就是我们现在要打开的那两个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Cool, so those are the two
that we're gonna turn on right now.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后在下面我们再做一件事，其中一个是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then down here we
gotta do one more thing, one of them is
在 env，此处，设置， >> Brian Holt: 和反应。
underneath env, here, settings,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And react.
>> Brian Holt: 然后你必须告诉埃斯皮林的 React 版本
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then you have to
tell eslint which version of React
你在用
you're using.
但是你也可以说，你能自己弄明白吗 ?
But you can also just say,
can you just figure it out yourself?
这就是检测的结果。
So that's what detect does.
>> Brian Holt: 这意味着它会从您的 package.json中找到它。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Which means it'll
figure it out from your package.json.
> > Brian Holt: 在这个时候我会告诉你，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
at this point I'll tell you,
这是我几乎在所有项目上使用的 React 配置。
this is my React config that I
use on almost all my projects.
>> Brian Holt: 非常好。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's pretty good.
我要说的一件事是 eslint 反应/建议有一些规则
The one thing I'll say here is eslint
react/recommended has some rules that I
也不一定同意。
don't necessarily agree with.
我想我们最终会把更多的人关掉
And I think we'll actually end up
turning a few more of them off later.
所以就因为反应/建议说的是一条规则，
So just because react/recommended
says something is a rule,
你可以有点问题
you can question it a little bit.
而不要在 eslint : 建议的内容中询问任何内容
Whereas don't question anything
in eslint:recommended,
那是真理的真理对吧
that's gospel truth right there, right?
你可以用它说的一切都很好
That one you can just,
everything it says is great.
重新获取 / 推荐，您可以对其中的内容进行提问。
react/recommended, you can
question what's in there.
>> Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay.
> > Brian Holt: 那么现在，如果我保存它，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now, if I save that,
你会注意到这不再是红的了
you'll notice now that
this is not red anymore.
实际上如果我评论它，它会说，嘿， React 必须在范围内，或者
And actually if I comment it, it's gonna
say, hey, React has to be in scope or
这不会有效的对吧
this isn't gonna work, right?
所以现在要用更多的 React 内容来帮助你
So it's actually gonna help you
out with more React stuff now.